[{
    "question": "Man: Do you spell your name with_____ without an \"e\"?<br>Woman: It's Anne with an \"e\".",
    "options": ["a. or", "b. for", "c. but", "d. and"],
    "answer": "a. or"
}
,
{
    "question": "Woman: Where did you______ last night?<br>Man: A new pizzeria in town.",
    "options": ["a. go", "b. been", "c. went", "d. going"],
    "answer": "a. go"
}
,
{
    "question": "Salesperson: I'm sorry, were you waiting long time?<br>Customer: No, I've only been here_____ a few minutes.",
    "options": ["a. since", "b. from", "c. for", "d. in"],
    "answer": "c. for"
}
,
{
    "question": "Woman: Did you and Sally go to the meeting last night?<br>Man: No, _____ couldn't go. Sally wasn't well.",
    "options": ["a. she", "b. they", "c. we", "d. I"],
    "answer": "d. I"
}
,
{
    "question": "Man: What do you usually _____in the evenings?<br>Woman: I like to watch Netflix.",
    "options": ["a. do", "b. doing", "c. done", "d. did"],
    "answer": "a. do"
}
,
{
    "question": "Man: speak to Mr. Brown, please?<br>Woman: He's not here, I'm afraid.",
    "options": ["a. Would", "b. Could", "c. Do", "d. Should"],
    "answer": "b. Could"
}
,
{
    "question": "Girl: _____I thought it was a bit boring.<br>Boy: Me too. The other team didn't get the ball very much.",
    "options": ["a. are they", "b. didn't they", "c. do they", "d. did they"],
    "answer": "d. did they"
}
,
{
    "question": "Man: Do you like Rosie?<br>Woman: She's OK but she doesn't say much.<br>Man: Yes, she's a bit_____.",
    "options": ["a. shy", "b. silly", "c. kind", "d. calm"],
    "answer": "a. shy"
}
,
{
    "question": "Boy: What's the homework for tonight?<br>Girl: The teacher_____ us to revise the irregular verbs.",
    "options": ["a. gave", "b. told", "c. spoke", "d. talked"],
    "answer": "b. told"
},
{
    "question": "Man: I _____ failed the test.<br>Woman: Frankly, it's a surprise to me.",
    "options": ["a. none", "b. no", "c. any", "d. not"],
    "answer": "d. not"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Is _____ any cake in the fridge?<br>Man: Yes. Help yourself.",
    "options": ["a. it", "b. here", "c. that", "d. there"],
    "answer": "d. there"
},
{
    "question": "Wife: I can't find my keys anywhere!<br>Husband: Oh, look! They're _____ the kitchen floor.",
    "options": ["a. on", "b. by", "c. at", "d. in"],
    "answer": "a. on"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Good morning, may I help you?<br>Man: Yes, I _____ that you sell laptop computers. Where can I find them?",
    "options": ["a. was telling", "b. did tell", "c. was told", "d. been told"],
    "answer": "c. was told"
},
{
    "question": "Man: Beautiful curtains!<br>Woman: Thanks, I made them _____.",
    "options": ["a. myself", "b. me", "c. my me", "d. my"],
    "answer": "a. myself"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: You play the piano, _____ you?<br>Man: No, I play the guitar.",
    "options": ["a. aren't", "b. haven't", "c. won't", "d. don't"],
    "answer": "a. aren't"
},
{
    "question": "Man: Will you be at John's party tomorrow?<br>Woman: Well, I'll come _____ I finish work in time.",
    "options": ["a. if", "b. while", "c. when", "d. unless"],
    "answer": "a. if"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Do you know Tony?<br>Man: Is he the one _____ son is a doctor?<br>Woman: That's him!",
    "options": ["a. Who", "b. Whom", "c. Which", "d. Whose"],
    "answer": "d. Whose"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: You play the piano beautifully!<br>Man: Thank you! _____ you like me to play another song?",
    "options": ["a. Should", "b. Do", "c. Would", "d. Will"],
    "answer": "c. Would"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Where did you get that book?<br>Man: Peter gave it to _____ yesterday.",
    "options": ["a. myself", "b. my", "c. mine", "d. me"],
    "answer": "d. me"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Is your sister _____ television?<br>Man: No, she is not.",
    "options": ["a. watch", "b. watches", "c. to watch", "d. watching"],
    "answer": "d. watching"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: What's the name of Sam's new baby?<br>Man: I think she _____ Linda.",
    "options": ["a. names", "b. named", "c. will name", "d. was named"],
    "answer": "c. will name"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Come in, you look a bit cold.<br>Man: Thanks - the wind's so strong it nearly blew my hat _____.",
    "options": ["a. out", "b. off", "c. on", "d. down"],
    "answer": "b. off"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Look at this picture of my brother's new baby?<br>Man: You know, he looks just _____ your brother.",
    "options": ["a. as", "b. too", "c. like", "d. same"],
    "answer": "c. like"
},
{
    "question": "Man: What exactly do you want?<br>Woman: I would like to see you _____ good job on the project.",
    "options": ["a. to do", "b. doing", "c. having done", "d. do"],
    "answer": "d. do"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Hello! Can I _____ a message for Jim?<br>Man: Hang on! Just let me find a pen.",
    "options": ["a. say", "b. give", "c. drop", "d. leave"],
    "answer": "d. leave"
},
{
    "question": "Man: What's wrong?<br>Woman: My car _____.",
    "options": ["a. can't start", "b. isn't starting", "c. won't start", "d. doesn't starting"],
    "answer": "c. won't start"
},
{
    "question": "Boy: Do you like playing this computer game?<br>Girl: _____ boring. Shall we choose something else to play?",
    "options": ["a. It's", "b. They're", "c. I'm", "d. You're"],
    "answer": "a. It's"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: There is a green scarf on the chair. _____ is it?<br>Man: It isn't mine. It might be Ben's.",
    "options": ["a. Who", "b. Whom", "c. Which", "d. Whose"],
    "answer": "d. Whose"
},
{
    "question": "Wife: Do you fancy going to that new restaurant in town?<br>Husband: Oh, I'm really tired. Let's eat _____ this evening.",
    "options": ["a. in", "b. at", "c. out", "d. about"],
    "answer": "c. out"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: Oh dear, I've left my gloves in the car.<br>Man: Don't worry, I'll get _____ for you.",
    "options": ["a. it", "b. them", "c. some", "d. ones"],
    "answer": "b. them"
}
]